discgolfscene.com 2016-03-13

# Privacy Policy | The DiscGolfScene

Welcome to the DiscGolfScene.com website (hereafter referred to as the "Website”). Your privacy is important to us. We provide the following notice explaining our privacy and information practices for this Website to you. 

This statement outlines our privacy policy (our "Policy"). When you use the Website or provide information to us (including by completing an entry, registration or other form), you agree to the terms of this Policy. We may make changes to this Policy, without notice to you, from time to time and any such changes will become effective 7 days after being posted. You are responsible for checking periodically for changes. By accessing the Website, you indicate your agreement to and acceptance of the terms of this Policy, and consent to the collection, retention and use of your personally identifiable information consistent with this Policy, as amended from time to time. If you are visiting our Website from outside the United States, there may be special rules or limitations on your use of the Website. 

## Types of information we collect

We may collect certain limited information about you when you visit the Website. Such information might consist of your name, if you provide it, e-mail address, geographic location and computer identification. 

## How we collect the information

The Website may use cookies to collect information about your computer in order to facilitate your use of the Website. For example, when you visit the Website, cookies allow us to recognize you, and then when you return to our website, they allow us to customize your views of the Website and store information such as the scores you post, your friends and so on. Cookies do not allow us to personally identify you beyond the information you provide on the Website, but help us improve the quality of your visit to the Website. We also collect information that you provide to us when you register to establish a profile page. Such information might consist of your name, if you provide it, e-mail address, geographic location and computer identification. 

## How we use the information you provide us

We will use the information that you provide us only to facilitate your use of the Website. We will not transfer or sell information about you to any third parties except to a business partner which operates the Website. If we should ever file for bankruptcy or merge with another company while we still have any personally identifiable information collected through this Website, or if we should decide to buy, sell or reorganize some part or all of our business, we may be required to disclose your personal information to prospective or actual purchasers or receive personal information from sellers. 

Although we will protect your privacy on the Website as described in this Policy, you should keep in mind that if you voluntarily disclose personal information online, that information may be accessible to others. This is also true if anyone else has access to your personal computer, such as an employer or family member. However, if you link to a third party website from the Website, any information you reveal on that website is not subject to this Policy. You should consult the privacy policies of each website you visit. 

We may be required to disclose your personal information such as your name, if you provide it, e-mail address and computer identification if we believe it is necessary to comply with legal process (such as a court order, subpoena, search warrant, etc.), or other legal requirements of any governmental authority; would potentially mitigate our liability in an actual or potential lawsuit; is otherwise necessary to protect our rights or property; or is necessary to protect the interests of other users of the Website. 

## How we protect the privacy of minors

We will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from any person under the age of 13 without prior verifiable parental consent. We also do not knowingly collect personal information from anyone under the age of 13, or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 13, you should not attempt to register for the Website or send information about yourself to us. 

If we become aware that a user of the Website is under the age of 13 and is without verifiable parental consent, we will remove any personally identifiable information about that person from our files. 

## Links to other websites and services

The Website may contain links to other websites that we do not control; those websites have their own policies and procedures regarding privacy. We recommend that you review those policies before entering those websites, as we have no responsibility for any linked websites. We simply provide those links for your convenience. 

## Visitors located outside of the United States consent to this Policy

Privacy laws differ across the globe. If it is necessary for the purposes for which you have shared personal information with us for us to share your information within our global operations, we will do so consistent with this Policy. 

This site is hosted in the United States and is intended for United States visitors. If you are visiting from the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from United States law, please note that you are transferring your personal data to the United States and by providing your personal data you consent to that transfer. When you provide personal data to us or our service providers or vendors, you consent to the processing of your data in the United States as the site is operated in the United States. 

This Policy was updated on October 13, 2008.  
Use of the Website is subject to our Terms of Use.
